chrome-wallpapers.com 2018-12-20

# Privacy & Cookie Policy – Best Wallpapers & New Tab Themes

chrome-wallpapers.com (“chrome-wallpapers.com”), respects the privacy of users of our home. chrome-wallpapers.com website and related services, and has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. These privacy policies (the “Privacy Policy”) are intended to describe for you, as an individual who is a user of the chrome-wallpapers.com website or related application(s) or service(s) (hereafter, collectively, the “chrome-wallpapers.com Products,” “chrome-wallpapers.com Homepage” or “Website”) the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using any of our chrome-wallpapers.com Homepage Products or transacting business with us. By using any of the chrome-wallpapers.com Homepage Products, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.  
If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
In General. We may collect personal information that can identify you, such as your name and email address, and other information that does not identify you. When you provide personal information through any of the chrome-wallpapers.com Homepage Products, the information may be sent to servers located in the United States and other countries around the world.  
Information you provide. We may collect and store any personal information you enter on or via the chrome-wallpapers.com Homepage, including personal information that may be contained in any video, comment or other submission you upload or post. This may include identifying information, such as your name, email address and, depending on your submissions, your address, phone number and/or likeness. We also may request information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information.  
Information from other sources. We may also periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from other chrome-wallpapers.com businesses, business partners, contractors and other third parties and add it to our account information or other information we have collected.  
Information about others. We may also collect and store personal information about other people that you provide to us. If you send others (friends, relatives, colleagues, etc.) a product as a gift, information that may interest them or messages (such as invitations) through any chrome-wallpapers.com Homepage Product, we may store your personal information, and the personal information of each such recipient. Similarly, if you use the Website to upload, share and/or distribute content (including videos, comments or other submissions), and such content contains personal information about others, such information may be stored in order to allow for such uploading, sharing and/or distribution.  
Use of cookies and other technologies to collect information. We use various technologies to collect information from your computer and about your activities on our site.

Information collected automatically. We automatically collect information from your browser when you visit the chrome-wallpapers.com Homepage. This information includes your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us (see “Cookies” below), and the referring website address.  
Cookies. When you visit the chrome-wallpapers.com Homepage, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our site(s) and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site(s), such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site(s). Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the features offered on or via certain chrome-wallpapers.com Homepage Products.  
Other Technologies. We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of the chrome-wallpapers.com Homepage. We also may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our Website visitors to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities.  
Information collected by widget providers and other third-parties. When using the chrome-wallpapers.com Homepage, you may have the ability to add certain widgets (i.e., small embeddable computer files comprised of computer code, including XML, HTML or JavaScript) to your homepage and, if you have downloaded a chrome-wallpapers.com toolbar, to add widgets directly to your toolbar. Many of the widgets made available on the chrome-wallpapers.com Homepage are provided by one or more third party vendors. The use and information gathering practices of any third party-provided widget is governed by the relevant widget’s terms of service and privacy policy, which should be available via the widget itself or at the widget developer’s website. In addition, we may allow third-parties, including our authorized service providers, widget providers, chrome-wallpapers.com companies, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements or place ad tags or beacons on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Unless expressly stated otherwise, our Website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness.

**NOTICE REGARDING USER-GENERATED-CONTENT**

We do not screen, filter or monitor user submissions made to or via the Website or any widget made available via the Website, nor do we scrape or glean personal information from any such submissions; however, to the extent that any video, comment or other user submission contains personal information (whether name, likeness, address, telephone number or otherwise, and whether such information pertains to the submitter or someone else), such personal information may be viewed by other users of the Website or relevant widget. See “USER SUBMISSIONS”, below.

**THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES**

There are a number of places on the chrome-wallpapers.com Homepage where you may click on a link to access other websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you use the functionality of certain widgets, or click on a news link, search result or advertisement, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all third-party websites you visit by clicking on the “privacy” link typically located at the bottom of the webpage you are visiting.

**USER SUBMISSIONS**

We may provide areas on the Website or via one or more widgets where you can post information about yourself and others and communicate with others; upload content (e.g. pictures, videos, audio files, etc.); and post comments or reviews of content found on the Website. Such postings to or via the Website are governed by our Terms of Use; such postings to or via any third party-provided widget are governed by the relevant widget’s terms of use. In addition, such postings may appear on other websites or when searches are executed on the subject of your posting. Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. Once you have posted information, you may not be able to edit or delete such information.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

Our website is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

**NO RIGHTS OF THIRD PARTIES**

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the website.

**END OF DOCUMENT.**

**GLOSSARY:**

**Cookies:**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record keeping purposes. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate our website. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time.

You may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. (Click “Help” in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.) If you do so, some of the features and services of our website may not function properly.

We may allow third-parties, including widget providers, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. The Website does not provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver, and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third-party’s privacy policy. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness.

**Web Beacons:**

Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies which are stored on the user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on the web pages (or in email) and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. We also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website.

Post: 061 Budapest, Andrássy út 35. 1/8. Hungary
